You never can tell. No, no, you never can tell. (Applause and cheers) Thank you.
Nunca se sabe. No, no, nunca se sabe. (Aplausos y ovaciones) Gracias.
I recently had the tremendous opportunity of searching for gold in the vast mine of songs released by Chess Records, a Chicago-based label that was really very active in the '50s and '60s in the US and that music spread all over the world. And the songs that I'm singing tonight are from an album that I just put out called, "Playing Chess," that pays homage to those songs. And these guys were really the innovators of rock 'n' roll and soul and R&B as we now know it. (Applause) (Music) (Singing) Over the mountain, across the sea, there's a girl waiting, she's waiting for ... me. (Music) Over the river, beyond every cloud, she's passed the wind blowin' loud. Over the mountain, a girl waits for me. (Music) Tell the sands, every blade of grass, please tell the wind to let my love pass. Over the mountain, a girl waits for me. Tell the moon up -- up in the sky. Tell all the birds that fly on by that over and over the mountain ... my love waits for me. Oh, into each dark, starry night, oh, what a mystery that's sealed so tight. Over the mountain, a girl waits for me. Tell the moon up -- up in the sky. Tell the birds that fly by that over and over the mountain my love waits for me. Into each dark and starry night, oh, what a mystery that's sealed so tight. Over the mountains,
Hace poco tuve la gran oportunidad de hurgar en la inmensa mina de oro que es la colección de canciones publicadas por Chess Records, una compañía discográfica de Chicago, muy activa en los 50 y los 60 en EE. UU. Esa música circuló por todo el mundo. Los temas que voy a cantar esta noche pertenecen a "Playing Chess", el álbum que acabo de lanzar y que le rinde homenaje a esas canciones. Estos músicos realmente inventaron el rocanrol, el soul y el R&B tal como los conocemos hoy. (Aplausos) (Música) (Cantando) Más allá de la montaña, del otro lado del mar, hay una chica que espera, espera... por mí. (Música) Cruzando el río, más allá de todas las nubes, más allá de los vientos. Más allá de la montaña, una chica me espera. (Música) Dile a las arenas, a cada brizna de hierba, por favor dile al viento que le abra paso a mi amor. Más allá de la montaña, una chica me espera. Dile a la luna, la luna allá en el cielo. Dile a los pájaros que pasan volando que mucho más allá de la montaña... me espera mi amor. Oh, en cada noche oscura y estrellada, oh, qué misterio tan bien guardado. Más allá de la montaña, una chica me espera. Dile a la luna... la luna allá en el cielo. Dile a los pájaros que pasan volando que mucho más allá de la montaña me espera mi amor. En cada noche oscura y estrellada, oh, qué misterio tan bien guardado. Más allá de las montañas,
a girl waits for me. She waits for me. Oh, she waits for me. I know, I know, I know, I know, I know. Oh, I know, I know, I know, I know, I know, oh oh, oh oh. (Applause and cheers)
me espera una chica. Ella me espera. Oh, ella me espera. Lo sé, lo sé, lo sé, lo sé, lo sé. Oh, lo sé, lo sé, lo sé, lo sé, lo sé. lo sé, lo sé, lo sé, lo sé, lo sé, oh oh, oh oh. (Aplausos y ovaciones)